dex-digital.com 2013-04-30

# •

PRIVACY POLICY
Last Updated March 27, 2012
Dex One Digital, Inc. d/b/a Dex Digital (collectively, "Dex Digital") understands and respects your concerns about
privacy. We may from time-to-time revise this privacy policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of
this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. By visiting the Website (as defined in the Terms of Use),
you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after changes
have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.
What information we collect: Dex Digital may ask for and collect from you personally identifiable information at
certain points throughout the Website. Depending on the information and/or services you request, you may be asked
to provide your name, email address, and other information. Once you provide your personal information, you are not
anonymous to Dex Digital.
In addition to the information you knowingly provide, Dex Digital collects the domain names and IP addresses of its
visitors, along with usage statistics (e.g., types of web browsers and operating systems used) and browsing history.
In addition, Dex Digital may collect information, including personally-identifiable information, related to your usage of
other Dex Digital (or its affiliates) websites and third-party sites that you access through the Website. Dex Digital also
may store emails that you send through the Website. This data is used to more efficiently operate Dex Digital's
business, promote and measure the effectiveness of our products and services, and administer the Website. Dex
Digital may combine this information with the personally identifiable information it collects.
How Dex Digital uses your information: Dex Digital may use your information:
     •    To provide you with personalized content.
     •    To process and respond to inquiries.
     •    For the purposes for which you provided the information.
     •    To improve the content and navigability of the Website.
     •    To alert you to new Website features, special events, products and services, and to deliver newsletters from
          which you may opt out.
     •    To promote, measure, and improve the effectiveness of Dex Digital’s products and services.
     •    To enforce the Terms of Use.
In the future, we may sell some or all or our assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the
transferred business assets. In the event of a sale of our assets including our database, customer information will be
transferred. We will contractually require buyers to honor our privacy policy.
Information Sharing with Unaffiliated Third Parties: Dex Digital may disclose your personally identifiable
information to another entity (i) for purposes of outsourcing one or more of the functions described in the previous
section; (ii) to confirm or update information provided by you; (iii) to inform you of important information; and/or (iv) as
a part of a sale of assets as described in the previous section. We may also share your information in response to a
subpoena, legal order, or official request, when we believe you have acted in violation of the Terms of Use or when
we believe that doing so may protect your safety or the safety of others.
Information Sharing with Affiliated Companies: We may share your personally identifiable information with other
companies in the Dex Digital family, business partners and network partners, and will require the recipient to comply
with the provisions of this privacy policy.
Sharing and use of de-identified information: Information that is de-identified (stripped of any information that
could be used to identify you) may be used by Dex Digital for any reason and shared freely with affiliates, partners
and other third parties. This information is usually aggregated (combined with information from many other users),
and may include information such as traffic patterns, trends in connection with various types of inquiries, and other
information.
How we collect information: In addition to the methods described above, we may also collect information using
cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies. These methods permit us to collect various types of information,
including which pages you visit, which of our email messages you read, and other information.

How we protect information: Dex Digital attempts to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal
information. Our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures. Please note,
however, that electronic transmissions via the Internet are not necessarily secure from interception, and we do not
guarantee the security or confidentiality of such transmissions or their storage.
How you can view or update your personal information: To ensure that you have as much control over your
personally identifiable information as possible, you may update your information by contacting us at
customercareemail@dexone.com. We will use reasonable efforts to process any change you make; provided,
however, that requests to delete information are subject to Dex Digital's internal reporting and retention policies and
all applicable legal obligations.
Targeted Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Some of
these companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about
your visits to Dex Digital and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be
of interest to you. To learn more about this practice, its benefits, or about your choice to opt-out of this practice, see
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Children: This Website is not directed toward children under 13 years of age nor does Dex Digital knowingly collect
information from children under 13. If you are under 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information
to Dex Digital.
Links: The Website may contain links to third-party websites. Dex Digital is not responsible for the privacy practices
or the content of such websites.
Your California Privacy Rights: If you are a California resident, you are entitled by law to request an Information
Sharing Disclosure. If you request it, we will provide you with a notice of your right to prevent sharing of your personal
information as well as a cost-free means of doing so. To receive such a notice, submit a written request to the
address listed in the Contact section below, specifying that you seek your "California Customer Choice Notice."
Please allow thirty days for a response.
Contacts: If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at
customercareemail@dexone.com.
